Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching!
Good evening, everyone.
Good evening.
The morning chimes have rung. It's us.
℃-ute.
I, Kazami, will be your host today.
I'm a little nervous today with Aya and Miyuki, but I'll do my best. I'll do my best.
I'm Yatsumoto. I am Yatsumoto.
I am Hoshino.
Let's begin.
Ebichu's Delightful and Funny Showroom.
Thank you very much for watching the 42nd Ebichu's Delightful and Frivolous Showroom today.
Ebichu's Delightful and Frivolous Showroom is the sister show of our sister showroom, Uka's Showroom.
Let's do a ranking.
Ranking.
Then I'll say it.
Fifth place, thank you, Tsuna-san.
Fourth place goes to Maropi, thank you.
Third place goes to...
It's changed, hasn't it?
Thank you, Ji-kun.
The 2nd place goes to Tamamin-san.
Thank you very much.
The 4th place went to Shumai.
If you register with SHOWROOM and get an original avatar, you can get a free avatar for free,
You can get it by registering with SHOWROOM and giving a gift either for free or for admission.
What do you think?
There are a lot of them.
There are a lot of them today.
They are all really peculiar, aren't they?
Catchy, isn't it?
I'm glad. Please take this.
And please help us spread the word on Twitter by clicking on the Twitter symbol at the bottom of the screen.
So this is the time to spread the word.
In order for as many people as possible to see this broadcast, I'm going to tweet an announcement on Ebichu's Twitter now,
Please retweet it.
What are you going to do? Pose.
It would be good if you have a pose.
Something.
I've been posing like this lately.
The opposite.
Thank you very much.
How are things going lately?
Recently, we had the FC event on February 11, and I wonder if any of you came.
Thank you very much.
FC event.
This time it was a pajama party.
That's right. The theme was a pajama party,
Each person wore different pajamas,
What kind of pajamas are you wearing?
Yes. I got a call.
I thought to myself, "Well, I'm wearing a pair of Gerapique pajamas this time of year.
I'm wearing Gerapique pajamas this time of year,
When I said "fluffy," I thought it would be too hot for live performances,
I told him that I was wearing pajamas made of a slightly dry fabric that I wear in the summer,
Thank you very much. It was so cool.
They looked so cute.
I heard it was a Valentine's Day collaboration with Gerapique.
Can I get one of those?
I want one!
I want pajamas, don't you?
I want them.
I'm sure you do.
I'll get them later.
I'll have them later.
Nonaka's were also smooth.
You were right again.
That was cute.
Was he really wearing that?
It's probably almost the same as the one I wore at the camp,
The pattern is just a little different.
That's right.
Gatchin pajamas.
What about you, Aya?
Where's Aya?
Aya was so cute.
She was fashionable.
She was stylish. A little bit, fashionable.
Maybe a little bit more spacious in real life,
But I made her a little stylish.
Wearing glasses and so on.
That's right.
I've seen you before, Aya.
Have you? Yes, I have.
She came out with a ding dong.
But sometimes she wears sunglasses?
That's a joke.
He puts them on as a joke.
He comes out with a bang and puts on sunglasses.
It was kind of funny.
That was hilarious.
Including the glasses.
Aya's glasses.
Rika's were fluffy ones.
Rika's was a collaboration of Evangelion and Peach Jean.
It's really her version of that kind of collaboration, too.It's really her version of that kind of collaboration and so on.
The manager prepared it for me according to what I liked.
It was cute.
I heard she used it.
I knew she was the one.
Even I can't do it.
Even I can't do it. These pajamas would kill me.
But they were cute.
She was cute.
There was a guy who came from Malaysia.
What?
In the comments.
That's amazing.
From Malaysia?
There was a person who came from overseas.
That's amazing.
It was the first time for him to see our site.
I'm so happy.
Here it is.
Malaysia.
Really?
That's great.
Did you get it?
Thank you very much.
That's a great guideline.
Really?
That's great.
What does it say?
Fuck you, Eiffel Tower.
How do you read that?
Is it Malaysian?
Is it a Malaysian name?
Thank you very much.
It's close to Chiba, isn't it?
I would like to go to Osaka.
I'm watching from Japan.
That's pretty much it.
Where is the Italian restaurant? Saizeriya?
Saizeriya.
I've made up my mind.
This is Nonaka's first time at a fan club event, right?
How was it?
The set was really cute,
I really liked it.
It was really fun.
The three of us performed our solo songs,
Nonaka sang Ayaka's "Erwin" again.
I sang,
I was so nervous and thought a lot about how to express myself,
I discussed it with Ms. Emiko,
The day before the performance, I had a voice training session,
I had a boy training the day before, so I didn't move during the rehearsal,
We discussed the idea of standing in the center of the stage and walking around a bit.
I was very anxious about it,
I was very anxious,
But when I asked Aya about it, she said it was good,
So I'm glad.
I was nervous, but it was very typical of Nonaka.
I thought it was a song that could only be sung by someone of Nonaka's age.
Did you give her any advice, Yasumoto-san? Because.
Advice.
What did I say?
I remember.
The lyrics of "Will we meet again?
I think each lyric changes the feeling of "Will I see you again?
I suggested that we change the expression. I said, "Why don't you change the expression?
That's great.
Isn't it amazing? I was.
You were saying that?
Yes, you were.
It was great. Because...
Thank you very much.
Shimeba's solo was great.
It was great.
We usually don't get to see when someone does a solo.
We can't.
Not live.
But at fan club events,
We could sit in the back and watch,
We can see the reactions of the fans in real life.
The expressions on the fans' faces as they watched the three of us,
It was like a mother and father.
It made me feel a little nostalgic,
It was just like when we first started doing things like this,
It was like when we first started doing all these things.
It was fun to be a part of it.
Yuno was on a rampage.
Yuno was amazing.
He was so funny.
Yuno is good at the show, isn't he?
I knew he was strong.
He was really giving it his all on the stage.
To be honest, the rehearsal was a mess,
I didn't know what was going to happen,
But it was really good.
I knew you were strong in the show.
It was a lot of fun.
It was great. It was good that we were able to get in between the two.Great. I'm glad you were just in between.
Let's play here was a cool feeling.
Including the dancing here and so on.
I like it.
All three of us were able to bring out the different feeling of each of us.
Look beyond the door,
Kaho-chan was checking.
She was directing it herself.
It was amazing.
It was great to see Yunotsuki on a rampage.
I'm glad. This one was good, too.
It was very mature.
Including the pajamas,
It's a mature atmosphere,
They're not like the previous members of Ebitune, but they're new.
It's like the 16-year-olds of today, isn't it?
In today's world.
Yes, I think so.
That's how I feel.
It was great.
It was a good fit.
It fit. It fit.
There was also a franchise event,
We ended up dressing up in costumes.
That's right.
We did cosplay of each profession.
It was a lot more than that.
Yeah, yeah.
It was fun.
And the full album is coming out on March 23,
And the song with all the members' voices is coming before that,
Yes, that's right.
We finally got to listen to all the songs we recorded,
We can finally listen to all the songs we have recorded, and for our fans, the songs that we have recorded,
We have announced who wrote the songs and what titles they are,
Who wrote the songs and what the titles are.
Yes, we did. We announced it.
I guess you could say we have a new lineup this time.
We had a very popular artist write the title of the song,
It's our first encounter with them,
We met for the first time in each genre,
There are songs from various genres on this album,
There are songs in various genres this time, but there are also songs in genres that we have never ventured into before,
In that sense, we had a lot of new encounters,
Recording was a lot of fun, wasn't it?
It was fun.
We always go home after recording,
We always go home talking.
Is that so?
That's our tradition,
Of course, there are times when the people who created the songs are also there,
We talk with the writers whom we have never met before,
We don't talk about the music at all.
The content of the conversation is really too public.
When I talked with Kate Aloha,
At first, she was very young. She was 21 or something.
She was 21 or something,
We started by talking about how she had been to the soundtrack and so on,
We talked about how she had never been to Disney,
We really talked about relationships,
We talked about relationships for about half an hour.
Sounds like fun.
Isn't it?
Was there a tradition?
I told him I had to work really hard.
I was nervous.
Tell me about this.
What was it? The last song Nonaka recorded?
The last one?
Second to last?
It was the last song he recorded.
What was it?
Was it the last one?
Second to last?
Second to last.
What was it?
I can't remember.
Second to last?
It's coming. I think it's coming.
I think it's coming, but I can't remember.
Let's see..,
The song,
The 7th was the day before.
So, what was it like? Like...
I asked him.
How did it feel? I asked him,
The recording went pretty smoothly this time, too,
I drank too much water,
I drank too much water and it took a while.
That's the first time I've heard such a thing.
I usually drink so much water during recording that I run out of a whole bottle.
On the 7th, I was really concerned about the time,
I wondered why he was so serious.
You are a caring person, aren't you?
I was surprised at how much he cared.
It's okay to drink water.
He told me to drink water, but not too much water.He told me to drink too much water and that I should drink water.
I was very dry.
It was pretty dry at the time.
And in the casuaries.
My throat was so irritated.
It was amazing.
It was really interesting.
Are you getting used to it now?
You take a lot of pictures for the album.
You took a lot of pictures for the album.
That's right. It took a couple of months,
But there was also a period of time when we condensed the shots,
Are you getting used to it? Recording?
Yes, I'm getting used to it.
But I'm getting used to being asked to do things this way,
I think I'm getting used to it.
That's a good thing.
It's true that once you sing a song, you can try a different pattern and try a different kind of expression,
I think that's a good thing.
It was a bit confusing at first.
That's true.
And when it comes to making an album,
And when you are making an album, after one song, the next song, and the next song, and the next song, and so on,
So the speed of learning goes up.
Like during the Momoiro Uta Gassen,
When recording was done the day after the school arts and crafts festival,
That's right.
The moment we finished the big show, we worked really hard,
I concentrated on learning the songs,
There were times when we worked until quite late at night.
It was a really fun album,
I was amazed at how many different genres this idol could sing,
I think it is an album that will really surprise you with how many different genres this idol can sing,
I hope you will all enjoy it on the 23rd.
I hope you all enjoy it on the 23rd.
So, what's going on with you, Yuka? Let's ask her.
What have you been doing lately? I mean, what have you been doing lately?
What have you been doing lately?
What have you been doing?
I made an appointment! I made an appointment. Thank you very much.
I think that all the fans who have loved us for a long time probably find it refreshing.
I think there will be.
I think they'll enjoy it.
Here it comes. What is it?
I went to the birth of Wrigley's birthday.
Hinata is doing her birthday tour now, and yesterday was in Sendai?
Sounds like fun. I want to follow her.
I want to follow her. I want to go as her manager.
I'd like to take care of you.
Thank you.
Oh, your sweater. She's going to Osaka now. What's that? Osaka tomorrow?
That's right.
I see.
See you in Osaka.
I'm watching a lot of anime to talk to Kazuyama.
I see. Stop it.
And online events.
Online storytelling and two-shot meetings are also a bonus for the album,
Was the deadline for the second round of applications until 2:00 p.m. today?
I think it was.
I think there will probably be another one at 3pm, so we are looking forward to seeing you all there.
I'm looking forward to talking to you all.
Yes, I know.
You're doing this for me.
Hmmm...
Young egret?
Pike fishing?
You fished for smelt?
Oh, no.
That's it, right? In a little hole in the lake.
Ah~.
I tried that.
It looks cold.
Was it cold?
Yes, it is.
Have you ever been fishing?
I did a YouTube project,
That's right. You did, didn't you?
It's difficult.
Difficult?
I just did a little tap,
I had to raise it,
But even then, it was too slow,
I was still too slow, and I got caught up.
It was difficult.
Can you touch a fish like this by yourself?
When I lifted it up.
When I was a little boy,
I used to go fishing with a fishing raft, and at the end, I drained the water,
I had a kind of fishing raft that I could catch the fish by myself,
I used to touch the fish with that.
It was amazing.
Do you remember when we used to do river fishing as part of a photo shoot?
Yes, we did. I remember that.
No one could touch the fish,
It was nice to catch a fish, but..,
You catch a fish, and then it moves a little bit.
You go in front of yourself.
That was the hardest part.That is the hardest part.
That was the hardest part.
It was difficult.
A certain person was pushing hard for the entrance examination.
He said he would work hard for one more week.
That's right!
I see.
It's the season of entrance examinations, and it's also the period of tests.
That's right...tests start tomorrow, on the 7th.
Tests today and tomorrow.
It's the final test of the school year, right?
Good luck, everyone.
Please do your best. One week to go.
Let's catch up.
How is the Atami trip going?
Yes, it is. I have a new calendar coming out,
This time, we went to the city of Atami and did a lot of things,
It was really just a day trip,
It was your first time, wasn't it?
It was my first time.
It was the first time for all three of us to shoot outside on a clock,
It was fun, wasn't it?
It really felt like a trip, didn't it?
Yes, it was.
Odawara, right? Odawara, right?
That's right. Odawara.
On that day, the three of us had a lot to talk about,
It was like it wasn't a job at all,
I felt like I was truly changed, and it was fun.
That kind of thing is fun, isn't it?
It was fun.
It's fun to work. It was in Odawara, wasn't it?
It was Odawara.
The people in Odawara told me not to get angry.
Stand up.
I think you can see a lot of the real Ebitu.
That's right. He has a natural expression on his face.
It was a warm day, so it was nice.
Yes, it was.
It was warm.
You saw Odawara-dera Temple from a distance, right?
Yes, I did.
I hope you will be able to get it.
Yes, I would love to have it.
Next, this corner.
A fun and fufu game of two choices.
Yay!
We are going to play a game of two choices for the February 2022 delivery.
We will ask you a question that divides you into two choices, the past or the future, and you will be divided into two groups and make a claim for each group.
Finally, the participants will announce which side of the argument they are on.
At this point, the goal is to have a 2 to 1 majority.
Those who are in the minority are punished.
And here is the most important point of this game,
If all three players have the same opinion, all three must play the penalty game together.
Yes, I see.
I see.
Yes.
I wonder if this is a game of punishment.
I guess it's a game of punishment.
I guess I'm going to start soliciting comments.
I see.
Punishments will be solicited in the comments.
Oh no! Absolutely no! Punishment game.
Would you like to play a 7-man tag team?
What's the theme?
What's the subject?
Yes. If you were to eat a steamed bun now, would you eat a steamed bun? Anmanman?
Uh...
No, I'm dead.
That's a tough one.
Are you hungry?
I'm hungry.
Not that hungry.
I'm...
I don't know.
I just ate an onigiri.
I had onigiri for dinner.
But I ate bread at home and had an onigiri earlier.
You feel really carbonated, don't you?
That's true.
But I'm in the mood for something sweet.
I'm a bit of an agasimo, aren't I?
What?
I just ate a little bit slowly.
I want something sweet.
A gift of meat buns and bean paste?
Oh, that's right!
They're currently throwing meat buns and bean-paste buns in the showroom.
I see!
What?
That's a lot!
You mean throw them to everyone, right?
You don't say?
A shooting star has come down, hasn't it?
I'm sure of it.
I've been in the mood for something sweet since I first got home.
Wait a minute!
I want a steamed bun now.
You want a steamed bun?
What about you, Aya?
Oh, I want a bean-jam bun.Oh, I want to eat manjuan.
I want to eat a manjuu too.
Oh, wait!
Wait a minute!
That's not good.
I have to make him want to eat a steamed bun.
I wonder what it is. But, bean-jam buns?
Don't embarrass the junior high school students.
Definitely bean-jam buns. I'm definitely eating bean-jam buns now.
I'm definitely having a bun.
I ate a lot of salty food earlier.
But I guess buns are different depending on the community.
There are all kinds.
And I don't know. It's so difficult!
Wait a minute!
If I don't do this, Marukaga!
Eyelashes stand out!
The steamed buns are delicious!
Delicious?
What? ! Manjuu!
Wait a minute. It's difficult.
You need to get all your fans on your side.
They'll make Aya and Mire-chan into meat buns.
Aya and Mire-chan will be made into meat buns?
They'll make you want to eat meat buns.
Everyone who is watching, please help the wild child.
Please give us comments that make us want to eat meat buns.
Manjuu meat buns.
Oh, I see. You don't mind if I don't go through too much, do you?
Yes, you can. That's not true. That's not true.
Why are you trying to get me or Ayaka to betray you?
Like, "Aya, if you betray me now, you can do it,
Mirei, betray Aya,
I heard that you're going to betray her and make her do the punishment game.
She's pretty honest. It's me and Ayaka now.
What are you going to do?
What are you going to do? Nonaka.
What should we do?
It's okay.
When there's a 5 x 5 x 1, and when there's not.
Don't tell me it's a three-man game.
Mirei, you know what I mean. Because...
Oh, man. All the fans are on Nonaka's side.
That's not good.
No, it's not. They're staring at me.
Don't look at me like that.
I feel like I'm in a ted store. Right now.
I feel like I should take him home.
The acrylic board goes well with it.
It's true.
Shall we go now?
Well, let's get it together.
Wait here. Nonaka, what are you going to do?
Wait.
I know you won't do that.
I'm sure he won't.
Are you watching?
I'm in.
Oh, no.
What is it? Maybe it's in the middle,
Mirei might end up betraying us.
But the middle one is the most likely to betray us.
Ready!
Yes, sir.
I'm beaten.
It's a good thing I didn't write only one person's bun.
That's for sure.
There were a lot of "meat buns" in there.
Then, let's all write something.
That's right. Which one should it be?
That's right. It's kind of hard to start from the beginning.
What do you want?
I said, "All the fans," so here we are.
We're all going to be punished.
Why?
We're all in the penalty game now... three of us... before the penalty game.
What would you like?
What?
There's so many of them.
What's the big meatball fight?
Does it mean we have to do it together?
Is there such a thing as a big steamed bun fight, or do I just not know about it? In the world.
What do you think?
Okay, the Great Steamed Manju Fight.
You have 10 minutes.
Who'll do it, then? Sensei, Sensei, what should we do?
Okay, Hoshina-sensei.
Please do it.
Nekuman gymnastics number one!
Tonton tonton tonton, yes, meat, meat, meat, meat, right, left, inside is a meat bun.
Tonton tonton tonton, yes, right, left, right, left, inside is meat bun, meat bun, meat bun.
Yes, it's a stretch, isn't it?
It's now a stretch for Akihabara.
That's wonderful.
I'm not moving at all, honestly.
It's moving like a weapon.
When is the CD coming out?
This is a CD, please don't make this into a soundtrack.
Limited.
Today only.Today only.
It's true, I'm being punished.
It's okay, Tenda-san.
Good.
Shall we proceed like this?
Second question.
If you were to be reborn for a day, would you be a dog? A cat?
I've already decided on this one.
I have a rule that I definitely want to be a dog.
I want to be a dog.
Wait, I tried to get a dog.
I want to be a dog, too.
I'm a dog, too.
Stop it!
That's the pattern.
Are you all dogs?
Nonaka's not a dog?
What? Because I have a dog and I see it. I see dogs in action.
Dogs move around a lot, get walked, and sleep,
It seems to be fun if only for a day, doesn't it?
Cats seem to stay in a quiet place all the time, so I prefer them to stay in a quiet place and have time to move around,
I see.
I see. I'm living in the real world on the way,
To be honest, cats are the kind of people who don't get too close,
I don't compare myself to a dog in that I can be so sweet to people.
I wouldn't be so sweet to someone like "Aya-chan, Aya-chan, Aya-chan" either.
If it were a dog, that would be 100% acceptable.
I want to be spoiled.
But now that I'm listening to you two, I'm thinking that cats would be nice, too.
Everyone thinks about it.
Then, go ahead, a cat.
No, no, no. First we have to talk about it.
A cat. Think about it, guys.
You know how they say cat girls are popular with the ladies?
So if you become a cat, you'll be popular.
But only for a day. You'll be popular as a cat.
It's fine, it's fine. You are a cat.
I'm a cat, so it doesn't matter if I'm popular with humans. In the state of a cat.
That's why it's a cat.
A kitty.
Isn't being a cat strong enough for a girl to be a cat?
Cats are strong.
She's cat-like. She's that kind of cat.
Even idols are cat-like, and they're always mocking at handshakes and such.
They immediately run to be popular.
Everyone is like that.
That's why cats are so cute. They are cute.
I don't really have that in me, and I suddenly realized that I admire it.
I know, right?
Mina-chan is cat-like.
You are cat-like.
That's why it's okay to be a dog.
We don't have the strength of a cat.
Dogs are looking at us closely, so they want to be dogs.
That's right.
Then, do you want to write?
Huh? This.
This.
What am I supposed to do with this?
I'll betray one of them.
Huh?
You can choose who betrays you now.
That's right.
Okay.
Ready, go!
I don't want it, I don't want it, I don't want it!
That's right!
I thought if I got lost, I'd just write "dog" on it and let you guys do it again.
I could do that too.
But I kind of trusted that Nonaka would write "cat".
What's a good punishment?
I'll pick one.
Pick one?
You're wanted.
I ran with my hands.
Shut up, shut up, shut up.
Don't do that, it's embarrassing.
What is it?
Doggy Gymnastics No. 1.
It's a doggy.
It's not a kitten.
What is it?
I wonder, a lot. It's an animal-related thing, after all.
Cat gymnastics.
Nyan cat pose? I can already afford kitten pose, can't I?
Well, I'm all over it.
Oh, I heard you are imitating a popular girl in the cat world.
That's difficult.
Imitating a popular cat in the cat world.
Popularity in the cat world?
To be Aya's ideal cat.
It's a little difficult.
Tell me when it's ready.
When it's ready, if there's something else you want to do until it's ready, please let me know.
Okay, I'll do that.I'm sorry, I'm not sure I understand.
It's hard... by the time I'm done, I'm gonna have to put a "nyan" at the end of the word.
That's good, isn't it? That's one of the most popular cats in the cat world.
You want to go with that?
For a while.
I'm getting bored with two gates.
So we'll just keep going until everyone says it's time to go.
And when I say it's okay, it's okay...
I'll put on my Meow.
I'm gonna be cute for the rest of the day.
I can?
I'll be cute.
Will I?
Next time, please be on my side.
Please.
Please!
Now that you've said please, let's move on to the next problem.
Let's move on to the next problem.
Yes, if you're taking me to a deserted island...
Coho, Coho, Rico...
Which one?
That's a no-brainer.
What? I don't know if I have a choice.
It's not that hard.
I deliberately chose the other one.
We'll discuss it.
I forgot about that.
I'm just following along.
Is it obvious?
It's up to you.
Well... But Riko...
But Riko had a really good idea at the Dotamba.
Do it.
Good.
She's the one who makes suggestions.
But Koho-chan...
She knows how to live with us.
He cooks meals for me.
I don't know...
With some leaves or something.
I thought that she would be able to
I thought I could do
Both of them are difficult.
That's why I think Koho-chan is more like
I'd say Coho-chan is more like a mother.
Riko is more like
more like a father's Nyan
In terms of characteristics
I'd like to have both.
Nyan
It's difficult.
Oh, it's difficult?
Maybe it's difficult.
The first thing that came to my mind was Kao.
That way.
Khao...
I think he can build us a boat.
And I think he can get us out of here.
I don't know.
Knowledge of what not to eat?
Rico says he can do anything.
We'll both be like, "Right, right, right.
It's going to be a disaster.
Like, "Oh, no, I can't eat this.
That's hard.
Riko goes back to the wild.
Heh.
Someone was thinking of making a boat.
It's like, when I'm with Rikon,
It's going to be an individual play in the end, isn't it?
Oh, that's true.
Baby, I've already had a safe time with you, so I'm going home. Bye bye.
I'll take care of it on my own, so you're on your own.
I got it backwards.
Ah, sure.
Wow, that's difficult.
First, it was Riko,
But Riko went back to the mountains, I think,
So where does she come from?
The wild Nakayama.
Riko is going back to the wild.
That's difficult.
It's difficult. It's difficult.
Then, what about Mineyan?
Kahonyan, I guess.
She's leaning towards Kaho.
I was thinking of Riko at first,
But I'm not sure.
Which one is Aya?
Which one is Ayaan?
I'm still wondering.
I'm looking at the two of them now.
Which one will you go for?
Just tell me.
Well, which is it? It's hard to decide.
But, Rikonyan.
No, no, no, no, no, Kaho.
It's difficult, this.
This is very difficult.
It's so difficult, this.
Do you want to try to write it?You want me to write it down?
I'm writing to write.
I'm Kahonyan, right?
Well then,
I'm Kahonyan.
Huh?
I'm Riko.
Ho-ho-ho.
Well, well, well, well.
Well, so that's how it is.
Huh? Wait a minute.
This is already..,
I don't know.
Okay.
Ready.
Wait a minute. Shut up.
Here you go.
Ready?
I saw it!
That's great!
I thought I was going to be the one to collect them, but they were all stowed away.
I did it!
Wow, not again.
I wanted to punish Mie-chan for that.
Ah.
I thought the same thing.
But, Ai-chan, today I understood.
It's not good to put people down.
It's not good.
It's true. When you do that, everyone is punished.
They're going to get stuck on you.
What do you want to do? What do you like?
This is difficult. Psychological warfare is difficult, isn't it?
It's difficult.
A morality show.
What is it?
Riko's impersonation?
Imitation?
Didn't you do my impersonation last time?
Oh, yes, I did a whole series of impersonations of everyone.
But I can do Riko's impersonation.
It's hard to understand, isn't it?
Then, let's talk as Riko for a while, shall we?
For a while?
I'll introduce myself as Riko.
I'll introduce myself.
Do you want me to go around? Okay, Riko's self-introduction.
Okay.
Okay, here we go.
Riko, please join me.
I'm going to Rikotan's event!
Wow!
Tantantantantan! Tantantantantan!
It's Riko! It's Riko! Ri-tan-tan!
No, it's not! No, it's not!
Yes!
T-tan-tan! T-tan-tan!
Ei-oh! Together, everyone!
This is Yamanashi Nakayama!
I'm Yamanashi Nakayama, attendance number 12 of junior high school students in Tatsuta!
Easy to get out!
Yay, yay, yay!
It looks like her!
Yes!
Next! Next!
Riko!
It's Riko!
Aiko! Aiko!
Aiko!
Did you eat that the other day? Aiko.
It looked delicious.
Aiko! Aiko!
I saw that drama!
I saw the drama!
Nonaka's so cute!
Wait, wait! Nonaka's cute!
Wait, wait! Nonaka!
He's the cutest.
Oh, you look like him.
You look just like him!
He's got your features, just like you.
Tatsuta no 2...
Tatsuta no 2, student.
Tatsuta's 2 students!
Too many lines, they all sound like lines, Nariko.
Tatsuta no Chugakusei!
When I sing, I say "dakuten
It's all "dakuten".
It's a dive, isn't it?
You've got guts.
Oh, it's delicious.
How was the rest of it?
I beg your pardon!
Excuse me!I beg your pardon!
Excuse me, Riko.
I beg your pardon.
Well, that's it!
That's all for now, and that's all for this fun and fluffy home game corner!
Yes, it's the end of the 42nd edition of Berryz's Delightful and Funny Showroom in the blink of an eye.
The end? Is this it?
Yes, that's right. It's the end.
The end.
The three of us are going to get along and play a penalty game.
Punishment game.
We're in love with each other.
It's the most punishing game, and it's the end of the seven times.
Yes. Can we see the announcement here?
Yes. Let's start with the announcements.
First of all, here it is.
Bischu Junior High School will be released on March 23.
I have already told you about it earlier,
Bischu Chugaku" will be released on March 23rd,
This is a work in which you will be able to see the various faces of Ebichu,
Please check it out.
And next?
Here it is!
Today, C-HEATS AB7X 10th Anniversary Tour 2022 Drawer will be held at 14 concerts in 12 cities.
It will be the first time for the three of us to go on a nationwide tour in a long time, so please come and enjoy the tour with us.
Hashigami Hinata is also currently on his birthday solo tour, and there are still some venues where tickets are available, so please come and visit us. Please come and visit us.
Please come and visit us.
Let's check the final ranking.
Fifth place, Hal King.
Thank you very much.
In fourth place, ZERORO7.
Third place, KANATA.
Thank you very much.
Second place, TATSU.
First place goes to TAMAMIN.
Thank you very much.
And that concludes the 42nd edition of Ebitune's Delightful and Fluffy Showroom.
And the next time will be the last as soon as it is decided.
This distribution will also include the reflection meeting that will take place after this distribution, so please check it out.
We will resume in a few minutes, so please stay tuned.
What did you think of the comments?
What did you think? How did you like it?
How was it?
This was Nonaka's first time as MC.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for shaking my hand.
No, no, no, no.
You've been very helpful.
Thank you very much.
He said you read better than your sister.
What did she say?
You're good.
Did you practice?
Practice. I read at home.
I knew it.
That's what I'm talking about.
That's the kind of girl she is. Nonoka-chan.
You did your best. Nonoka-chan.
Thanks for your hard work, everyone.
You were solid. Dododokamaru. Because of that.
Riko-chan.
Riko-chan said.
When did my nyan end?
Oh, that's right.
You finished it in a flash.
You played it in a good place.
Thank you very much.
If you have anything you want to tell us at the review meeting, please comment.
That's all for now, Shiri and Ebisu Junior High School.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching.
Different stories came in from different directions,
So the conversation starts and ends abruptly,
Sometimes someone speaks up on their own,
But the topic is taken away from me.
Most of the time, though, it's my friends who talk to me.
And one of them was a solid one.
Then I would change the subject.
When things get messy,
I'd give them a "psychedelic".
Not even a comic?
I tend to lean toward my younger friends.
So, I'll go for the smart one,
I'm the one who's smart and solid, and I'm the one who's going to give them a good talking-to.
It's a nice touch.
Are you a surprisingly playful character?
Surprising is unexpected.
I have a solid image of him, though.
I hear it's starting.
It's like a normal private conversation.
Thank you for your time.
Okay, Ms. Kasumi.
Is this your first MC?
Yes, it was.
How was it?How was it?
I was nervous,
During the first free talk,
I was wondering what to do,
but Miyu and Sheyashi did a great job of dividing up the conversation,
I wanted to do my best to talk about my own experiences,
I wanted to do my best to touch the conversation.
No, no, no.
Welcome.
No matter what mistakes you make,
They're all seniors who pick up on my mistakes,
I feel very safe.
It's overwhelming, isn't it?
Maru Nonaka did a great job. Maru Nonaka, you did great.
Maru Nonaka, great job.
I was glad to see him gradually relaxing.
Serious MC.
I heard that he was a very serious MC.
Everyone is looking at it from a parent's point of view.
Great. Great.
It's like attending a class.
That's for sure.
I thought they were very solid.
I wrote "ukka" in the big book,
He asked me if it was okay to call me Mr. Ukka.
They are the senior members of the group,
I just joined the group,
I wondered if I could call them "Ukka" at all,
I thought, "Let's change that. I asked if it was okay.
I told them in advance.
That's wonderful.
Another serious episode.
Nonaka's.
I heard about it during the recording session,
Sound?
We can't play the piano very well,
Nonaka can play the piano very well,
So, we would get the score.
We got the score.
Then, we would look for any differences in sound between the sound source and the music,
I asked the staff about all the differences in sound,
And then he would ask the staff about it,
It was amazing.
Is the score correct?
or the sound I was hearing in the demo?
Which one is he listening to today?
That's amazing.
I was shocked when I heard it from Wada-chan.
I was shocked when I heard it from Wada-chan,
But when I listen to the sound source, it is a little different,
But if you listen to the notes, it's different from the song and Ms. Kabayashi,
It's weird,
I wondered which would be better,
I wondered which one was better,
But not everything in the demo stage is correct,
So, I was wondering which one was better,
But everything up to that point,
It's amazing, isn't it?
It's amazing. That's great.
I remember it in a strange way,
I thought it would be difficult to fix it.
I want that ability.
That's great.
I want to say it too. I want to be aggressive.
That's not what I'm saying.
Then I just want to be aggressive.
That's great.
That's amazing.
You're paying such close attention.
Yes, I do.
That's great. I admire you a lot.
Really?
Now I feel like I'm going to do my best.
Thank you.
MCs grow more quickly when they are asked in such a serious manner,
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it. I'm looking forward to it.
It's all about accumulation, you know. This kind of thing.
That's right. I'll do my best.
Let's do our best.
Let's do our best without trying too hard.
Stay within the usual.
When I put out the cue, it's okay to read it after I've finished taking a breath.
Yes. Don't be in a hurry.
I learned it for the first time, didn't I? With today's timing.
That's right.
You want to read it right away, but you need to look at it with your eyes,
It's important to read it later.
With people like Mr. Mayama, it is natural for him to read the written copy as if it were his own words.
That's right. I always think about that.
It's amazing.
Your sister Mayama's.
That's amazing.
She's amazing.
And that's the other thing. Did you understand that it's not good to cheat people?
Yes, I do.
You have to suffer the pain yourself.
Yes, I did. Yes, I did.
It's amazing that you learned a lot.
Yes, I did. Today.
Shall we end with a cat?So, shall we end with a cat?
With a cat.
A cat.
Yes, I think so. Let's say goodbye to everyone.
Let's say goodbye to everyone.
Yes.
May I ask you to close the last part too? Meow.
Okay. Please do. Meow.
Thank you very much for today.
Nyan-nyan.
Bye bye.
See you in the next video.